oh look at
this this is a great place to have a
beer to stop over here though
major major win today
trailer
break yeah well the grades out here are
pretty bad too I had a couple really bad
grades just
now the turck is going to be long
downhills because those are going to
heat up the brakes big time but they hit
the brakes up no matter
what
so it's nothing my cashy can't
take I mean she's I'm sorry
guys so that's nothing she can't take
you know CU she's built for it she's
built the Long Haul like
that our
first happy
visitors I think a trailer break would
be a great idea honest to God I really
[Music]
do I if we could figure out how to make
that happen let me
know not to mention how do I park it on
a hill
right over the Divide I
know I know I know it's
like what wait till I have to for a
river that's a foot deep
what about that
right what about that what about foring
a river that's a foot
deep it's going to be a
hassle no
doubt cuz I'm I'm going to take her off
road that's why I got the the back
that's why I got the
the that's why I got those chunky
wheels so they can go up Road
she'll be fine if I lower the pressure
on the on the in the front and back tire
she'll be totally fine on
gravel because she's so stable you just
can't let her tip if she it's just like
writing it's like writing a reminds me
you know what now I'm starting to
remember it does remind me a lot of
writing a
motorcycle when when you ride a
motorcycle you cannot let it tip you
can't never come close to letting it tip
because you can't get it back up once it
falls
over and it's funny I just now that I'm
thinking about it those are it's it's
like it's like kicking in all my
motorcycle you know intuition it's like
don't you know start slow you know look
around for everybody because you're you
can't stop fast you know you never ever
want to Skid on a
motorcycle you know make sure you take
your Corners nice and easy it's like it
makes me into a really safe Rider which
you know is kind of interesting because
you know I got in trouble I lost my
teeth on that bike because I was going
too fast and I was going downhill with
no light on I would never do that on
this bike there's no way there's no way
I would do this on this bike I wouldn't
even go down that road on this
bike anyway
Good
Times super
happy I think I'm going to bring I think
I'm going to set up two
um I think I'm going to set up two Bell
boxes to stream on it at the same
time because the battery for the Bell
box is not that
bad because the Bell box does not have
to have any bizon backup does that make
sense oh there's the police officer I
hope I'm not breaking the law I think
I'm in the I think I'm in the beer
drinking
District super beautiful here
huh I could probably rig a rim break on
the back whe
yeah chalk the wheels I think you
probably am going to have to chalk the
wheels right it's a long haul
trucker cashy the long
hauler I cannot tell you how happy I am
that that just makes that the lines look
so good on that
trailer you
know I think I think we need to make
stickers do you think stickers can
somebody tell me
here I can to ask
chpt I don't have I don't have battery
God damn it did I bring one with
me I don't think I brought even a
battery with me I normally would should
bring one with me I'm going to lose
battery you know what I could do I
could I could run one from my my pack
actually yeah I could I could steal the
one
from I probably going to need to do that
let me go do that right now
how
much never mind looks like you got cut
off what were you asking
about what was I asking
about what was I asking about everybody
I was going to ask it about something I
can't
remember brain old man oh stickers right
thank you thank you thank you thank
you
um would putting stickers on my starlink
decrease the signal
strength stickers on the surface of your
Starling dish shouldn't affect the
signal strength much as long as they
they don't cover the entire dish or
interfere with the receiver it's best to
keep the dish as clear as possible for
Optimal
Performance what if I write on my
starlink dish with a marker will that
affect the signal at
[Music]
all writing on the Starling marker
shouldn't significantly affect the
signal
especially if it's just small markings
however it's still a good idea to avoid
covering large areas or making multiple
marks as any obstruction can potentially
degrade signal
quality I don't think we should put
anything on
it I I there's plenty of room for
stickers elsewhere you know what I mean
good call keeping the dish clear and
unobstructed will ensure the best
possible signal it's always best to
follow the manufacturer's
recommendations for optimal
performance all right
thanks you're
welcome this be harder to return that's
true I think I'm just going to leave it
and
then I'll put artx Rob on something
else I don't know what we'll like make a
banner or
something what we should do we should
make the traffic
side the traffic side paneer should have
a big old Banner on it so people from
the side can see can see what the what
the banner
says you know what I mean cuz people are
going to be curious they're going to be
like what the hell is
that and they're going to stop and
they're going to ask me about
it trying to think of how I could rig
that
up actually it's funny I actually
ordered jerseys and they didn't come
through so I ended up canceling them I
had jerseys that said RBX Rob on the
back yeah
I don't I mean that would be like merch
or
something I don't
know people people generally want to
see you know what else it's kind of a
believe it or not it's kind of a a theft
deterrent when when there's like a big
old sign on it and and everybody knows
that you're being
broadcast you would wear that would you
really
Mark are you capping me are you not
serious if you would wear an rwx Jersey
I'll get you
one do you want to do you want a jersey
or do you want a what I was thinking of
doing is getting like a BMX Jersey you
know what I
mean I have another question too so
right now I'm wearing the rig the POV
rig and I have a feeling that I'm
probably going to end up doing this more
than I thought
not C paint just a t-shirt is
fine get already best merch we should
probably eventually get merch going I
agree I think we should
too the first bike trip keshy the
starlink
babe keshy I am so proud of you for
being able to haul that thing
man no other bike that I have could pull
that [__] off my Fisher would Buckle
under that there's no way my Fisher
could do
that at least I don't think I definitely
couldn't put paneers on my
Fisher guys what do you think should I
should I save I have I have uh paneers
for the front forks but I think I'm
going to keep the anything cages and I'm
going to save the font front forks for
for water I'm going to put I'm going to
save them for
water I'm going to put a front frame
pack
on T-shirt with a picture of the rig
screened on it I totally you know what
else I'm going to do we got to get we
got to go to Adventure cycling in
Colorado adventure cycling historically
takes a picture of everybody's rig who
has done the trip
I don't want to tell my weight up front
you're right that's what I'm trying to
say I think water up front would be fine
I'm trying to figure out where to put
the water bottom
line I need to be able to carry 5 lers
of water and I'm thinking of I mean it's
kind of the next phase of this whole
thing is like where do we put all this
stuff
right um I hate heavy Forks they are
like so
squealy so I have my entire sleep kit my
entire tent kit goes into the right
anything cage bag and my entire cook kit
goes into the left anything cage
bag and I really like having it that way
because I can um I can take my cook kit
and I can combine it with my bear bag
and I can just take my bear canister and
and my and my cook kit and I can put
that wherever the hell and if the bear
gets to my cook kit I'm fine I don't
care if if and when a bear gets to my
cook kit because it smells like food you
know that means that nothing else on my
rig has got bear [__] on it has got
anything a bear would care
about so I'm going to put the frame I
have the front front frame pack I'm
going to put that back
on and then I'm going to put the mag the
mag um
what's it called the mag the mag part
that's like a good place to put snacks
and stuff and I'm going to put the
battery the battery for the phone the
rechargeable battery for the phone will
go
there and then I'm have a I'll have like
a 900 L milliliter 100 ml water bottle
on the on the only cages
there and then we'll do ay I and then
we'll do hey boobas you guys got boas
brought to you
free absolutely gorgeous young
women wearing cowboy boots no
L I am not wearing a helmet I'm going to
tell you right
now not I'm going to get I'm get a
cowboy hat I'm going to start wearing a
cowboy hat not even
kidding a cowboy hat is going to be my
regular thing I don't I go 10 miles an
hour guys
cool the bike Traer it does look like a
generator technically it is a
generator yeah there's there's a there's
a 1.26 KW hour battery in there that's
how you're streaming right now and
there's a 40 W solar panel on
there now the 40 W solar panel doesn't
do [__] I don't care because I can have
it I can have the 40 W solar panel
constantly recharging a Bas battery
you know what I'm saying O
probed cowbo has protect from Falls
everybody knows it play kinetic C charge
from recycling that would be great if
you could make it so you could actually
turn the wheels and have it
charge that would be so [__] awesome
by the way isn't my keshi beautiful look
at how gorgeous she is she's so [__]
beautiful I'm in love with you
keshi keshi you are the most gorgeous
bike ever you're so [__] beautiful
don't tell nah I said that I think
you're more beautiful than
her get a good size setson I know Ray
right and it do
charge I put a Dynamo on
there yeah I don't need no [__]
Dynamo
no no you know I can plug in my battery
and I can have 1.24 kilowatt hours in 90
minutes that's how long it takes to
charge it takes 90 minutes to
charge a
1.24 KW hour
battery actually scales
yeah that's a great idea
cryptocat yeah that's a great idea smart
yeah I'm reading the plaque the plaque
says John Franklin Moore 1822 to
1877 Pioneer citizen donor to land of
Civic use morisville was name in his
honor no [__] did not know that I've
been living here for 15 years I did not
know
that the battle of the battle of
Bentonville
chapter United Daughters of the federacy
1950 John Franklin Moore Pioneer citizen
donor of the land for civic use in
moresville was named in his honor John
Franklin Moore 1822 to 197 I've lived in
moresville for more than 20 years and I
had no [__] idea who it was named
after I am so
ashamed I feel really ashamed right now
it's like I it's like I took my own
personal Bike Tour Journey to my own
[__] hometown
I had never sat here I've never [__]
I've never read that historic I have
never read that historic plaque I had no
idea where morville the name morville
came from now I
know John Franklin Moore 1822 to
huh did you know Rosa Parks grew up here
she was a slave here yeah Rosa Park's
family family mother and mother and
father were slaves here in moresville
that's right I'm all about educating you
I know that Confederacy part I know he's
probably an
[__] he's probably a SL slave owning
[__]
6 love sided you [__] Yankee you know
what we should do we should like print
out a bunch of Yankee
stickers like deface Confederate
property you want to get me
shot no I no thank
you no thank
you you almost bought a a
cash had 21 from his son they were going
to do cross Contin divide bov stopped
him nice did you I love my mares man man
you know I sometimes you know what I got
I have the barend covers and I haven't
put them on yet I got the replacement
barend shifter covers they fall off
easily just say from New
York I'm going to need to start
traveling with a gun or some
[__] dude I this is the beginning of an
entirely new
life my friends I it might be the beer
talking but I got to tell you I am
[__] ecstatic right now every dream
I've ever had is coming
true I'm going to be able to tour the
entire continental United States and
make money doing
it I'm going to be able to check into an
agile scrum from the rim of the [__]
Grand
Canyon yeah uh yeah what was it I do I
don't have any blockers today no other
than the fact that I'm sitting on the
edge of the [__] Grand Canyon and
it's distracting
me cannot wait I cannot wait to phone in
to like an agile like weekly team
meeting from the [__] Grand Canyon I
am totally going to do that [__] and
people are going like hey why are you on
video today you normally you're just on
audio I don't know because I'm on the
edge of the Grand Canyon
like wait a second wait what how are you
working out there starlink baby starlink
baby and that's right I'm more
productive out here you know why because
it's awesome and there's no
distractions my Pimp's getting get so
D here's the
thing any project matters that gets
still over me being able to produce the
best possible [__] code I've ever
done because I am so ecstatic by working
on the road I'm actually going to be a
better worker because I'm going to be so
relaxed and
so ecstatically happy every day I'm
going to be the best possible worker
they could ever have I'm going to get
top marks every time and you know what
if for some reason they don't like it
fine fire my ass I'll go work for
somebody else or not I'll just [__]
retire early I don't care because I'm
going to do
it okay my entire how many ounces is
that my entire 25 full ounces of Corona
is now in my
system as you can hear in my voice my
voice has acquired a particular slur
oh hell yeah they're going to be jealous
you [__] kidding me my goal look I'm
going to write a book I've already
started writing a book about
this Ive already started writing a book
about this I'm going to say escape the
monotony be a digital Nomad by
bike why the [__] wouldn't you do this
I'm sorry that was really
loud if the technology exists why the
[__] would you not take advantage of
this
opportunity you can work remote you can
work you can have
250 kilobits per second download and 23
kilobit megabits per second
upload you can work more effectively
than having a [__] Spectrum internet
account at home in an apartment from a
starlink anywhere in the continental US
states any of the world why the [__]
would you not do that seriously at this
point why would you not do it
it's actually no more expensive I pay
$120 right now for internet access for
my
apartment think about that my
friends think about that I pay $120 to
Spectrum for internet access for my
apartment for my family at
home I pay
$150 for a$ 250 to 300 megabit download
23 megabit upload 33 second pain
from the starlink that I can take
wherever the [__] I want to
go why would you not do
it you need your three screens to
code well that's it that's a that's a
user issue